# **Brevin Tilmon**

Homepage: https://btilmon.github.io

Email: brevinjt@gmail.com Phone: 812-568-3344

## Background

Research and development of new imaging sensors to improve computer vision. Developing computer vision, computer graphics, and machine learning software and hardware (optics, electronics) solutions for sensors in embedded environments. Software engineering experience in C++, Python, PyTorch, OpenGL and CUDA.

#### Education

## University of Florida

5/2019 - 5/2023 (expected)

PhD, Electrical and Computer Engineering

## Murray State University

8/2015 - 5/2019

BS, Engineering Physics

## Experience

Snap Inc.

5/2022 - Present

Research Intern, Computational Imaging Team

Developing novel 3D sensors to improve 3D reconstruction on mobile devices.

Meta

8/2021 - 12/2021

Research Intern, Reality Labs

Developed dynamic occlusion prediction algorithm based on stereo cameras and machine learning.

## NASA Ames Research Center

5/2021 - 8/2021

Research Intern, Intelligent Robotics Group

Improved 3D reconstruction capabilities of embedded computational microscope.

## University of Florida

5/2019 - Present

Graduate Research Assistant, Florida Optics and Computational Sensor Lab

Research and development of computer vision algorithms and efficient cameras, projectors, and LIDAR sensors.

### Selected Publications, Patents, Open Source Software

(Please see my Google Scholar and GitHub for more)

- B. Tilmon. "illumiGrad: PyTorch-abstracted online camera calibration for RGBD cameras", GitHub 2022.
- B. Tilmon and S. J. Koppal. "Saccade Cam: Adaptive Visual Attention for Monocular Depth Sensing", IEEE/CVF International Conference on Computer Vision (ICCV), 2021.
- B. Tilmon, E. Jain, S. Ferrari and S. J. Koppal. "FoveaCam: A MEMS Mirror Enabled Foveating Camera", IEEE International Conference on Computational Photography (ICCP), 2020.
- F. Pittaluga, Z. Tasneem, J. Folden, B. Tilmon, A. Chakrabarti and S. J. Koppal. "Towards a MEMS-based Adaptive LIDAR", International Conference on 3D Vision (3DV), 2020.
- S. J. Koppal, Z. Tasneem, D. Wang, H. Xie and B. Tilmon. "Fast Foveation Camera and Controlling Algorithms", US16844597, 2020.